{
    "QuizList": [
        {
            "data": {
                "name": "Matematika",
                "description": "Quiz Matematika",
                "author": "EmangGek"
            },
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "100 + 120",
                    "answer": "220"
                },
                {
                    "question": "250 + 1050",
                    "answer": "1300"
                },
                {
                    "question": "0 x 100",
                    "answer": "0"
                },
                {
                    "question": "50 x 2",
                    "answer": "100"
                },
                {
                    "question": "1000 + 105",
                    "answer": "1105"
                },
                {
                    "question": "500 x 2",
                    "answer": "1000"
                },
                {
                    "question": "2 x 15",
                    "answer": "30"
                },
                {
                    "question": "10 x 15",
                    "answer": "150"
                },
                {
                    "question": "120 - 15",
                    "answer": "105"
                },
                {
                    "question": "1005 - 150",
                    "answer": "855"
                },
                {
                    "question": "120 / 6",
                    "answer": "20"
                },
                {
                    "question": "10 x 5",
                    "answer": "50"
                },
                {
                    "question": "500 / 25",
                    "answer": "20"
                },
                {
                    "question": "1 + 1 x 2",
                    "answer": "3"
                },
                {
                    "question": "50 + 20 x 100",
                    "answer": "2050"
                },
                {
                    "question": "25 / 2 x 10",
                    "answer": "125"
                },
                {
                    "question": "120 + 50 x 2",
                    "answer": "220"
                },
                {
                    "question": "50 x 2 + 1",
                    "answer": "101"
                },
                {
                    "question": "50 - 10 x 2",
                    "answer": "30"
                },
                {
                    "question": "50 - 10 x 4",
                    "answer": "10"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}